<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NOFA Kingway</title>
    <link>http://nofakingway.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NOFA Kingway</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 20:24:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://nofakingway.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Correcting Common Word Games</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/post/correcting-common-word-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 20:24:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/post/correcting-common-word-games/</guid>
      <description>These are some of the thinking-errors that we intend to correct over the coming months as we develop this site:
 postmodernism is anti modernism democratization is actually liberalization you own your body, your mind, and your life. no one has ever taken a life.  Find someone who claims to or is reported to have taken a life. Ask them to show you the other life, not their own life, but the life that they took.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake News, Fake Science, and You</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/post/fake-news-fake-science-and-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 18:18:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/post/fake-news-fake-science-and-you/</guid>
      <description>Media outlets and prominant intellectuals are rightfuly alarmed by the rising predominance of false and misleading news stories and social media posts. They are right to be alarmed, but they are wrong to suggest they were not complicite in the trend.
If cultural intellectuals, the type of who make value statements about culture, can be described by one sweeping term, that term would be &amp;ldquo;relativism&amp;rdquo;.
For quite some time the cultural climate has been one of cultural relativism, that supposedly all cultures are equal, and that has leaked into ideological relativism, the idea that supposedly all ideologies are equal, and that being certain of anything is the only true sign of ignorance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing Hugo Over DocPad</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/post/choosing-hugo-over-docpad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 21:04:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/post/choosing-hugo-over-docpad/</guid>
      <description>I love the flexibility of static generated sites. I can create content easily while I also develop the logical structure of the components and their taxonomical relations.
Most of that is provided by Markdown, including the YAML front-matter. So the static generator just needs to be easy to start and extend, and it also needs to be sustainable.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense to invest in learning how to use a static site generator that is not being actively used by a community of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Is fidelity to truth something you owe other people? Or, rather, is it something of the very highest importance to yourself?
What is the value of truth? &amp;ldquo;Do you want the truth?&amp;rdquo; This question is often used as a caricature of poorly written dialogue in movies and TV. Of course people want the truth, the criticism goes. At some point, at some level, every person realizes that they want the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing in Docpad</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/post/developing-in-docpad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 19:39:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/post/developing-in-docpad/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve started developing in Docpad because I love lo-fi text-only documentation. This CMS uses folder structure and tags for site hierarchy and is very flexible. The MarkDown is transpiled into html and I can use a variety of templating languages for the layout components.
I&amp;rsquo;m going under the assumption that this will all provide maximal flexibility while I am actively creating content.
Lo-fi Conceptual Representations I write a lot of notes every single day in MarkDown and yaml.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>