<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NOFA Kingway on </title>
    <link>http://nofakingway.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NOFA Kingway on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://nofakingway.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WALMART SHOOTER MANIFESTO</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/right-or-left/walmart-shooter/manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/right-or-left/walmart-shooter/manifesto/</guid>
      <description>Source MANIFESTO
The Inconvenient Truth About Me In general, I support the Christchurch shooter and his manifesto. This attack is a response to the Hispanic invasion of Texas. They are the instigator s, not me. I am simply defending my country from cultural and ethnic replacement brought on by an in vasion. Some people will think this statement is hypocritical because of the nearly complete ethnic and cultural destruction brought to the Native Americans by our European ancestors, but this just reinforces my point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questioning Socialism</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/books/the_house_of_government/questioning-socialism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/books/the_house_of_government/questioning-socialism/</guid>
      <description>When the ideals of socialism start to actually be implement their internal contradictions become alarming. Even devout advocates of socialism start to question the direction those ideals point.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nikolai_Bukharin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20181221</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/tweets/ethan11082658/20181221/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/tweets/ethan11082658/20181221/</guid>
      <description>1/ Re: your original post, belief and faith are the same thing. Your last sentence basically says &amp;ldquo;believe in belief&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;have faith in faith&amp;rdquo;. Perhaps you mean &amp;ldquo;have faith in religion.&amp;rdquo; That&amp;rsquo;s why I say serious confusion.
Further, validity is just a way of saying that your&amp;hellip;
2/ &amp;hellip; conclusion logically flows from your previously accepted premises. All premises are the starting point of an argument and presumably correct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Correcting Common Word Games</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/correcting-common-word-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 20:24:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/correcting-common-word-games/</guid>
      <description>The political landscape today is presented as an ever-changing battlefield between opposing factions, or &amp;ldquo;identity groups&amp;rdquo;. What is needed is not more opposing groups, but a better differentiation of ideals.
Sign Posts These are some of the thinking-errors that we intend to correct over the coming months as we develop this site:
 postmodernism is anti modernism   Democratization is actually liberalization  Democratization &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; Liberalization
More details&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake News, Fake Science, and You</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/fake-news-fake-science-and-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 18:18:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/fake-news-fake-science-and-you/</guid>
      <description>Media outlets and prominant intellectuals are rightfuly alarmed by the rising predominance of false and misleading news stories and social media posts. They are right to be alarmed, but they are wrong to suggest they were not complicite in the trend.
If cultural intellectuals, the people who make value statements about culture, can be described by one sweeping term, that term would be &amp;ldquo;relativism&amp;rdquo;.
For quite some time the cultural climate has been one of cultural relativism, the idea that all cultures are equal, and that has leaked into ideological relativism, the idea that all ideologies are equal, and that being certain of anything is the only true sign of ignorance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing Hugo Over DocPad</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/static-text-generation/choosing-hugo-over-docpad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 21:04:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/static-text-generation/choosing-hugo-over-docpad/</guid>
      <description>I love the flexibility of static generated sites. I can create content easily while I also develop the logical structure of the components and their taxonomical relations.
Most of that is provided by Markdown, including the YAML front-matter. So the static generator just needs to be easy to start and extend, and it also needs to be sustainable.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense to invest in learning how to use a static site generator that is not being actively used by a community of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Is fidelity to truth something you owe other people? Or, rather, is it something of the very highest importance to yourself?
What is the value of truth? &amp;ldquo;Do you want the truth?&amp;rdquo; This question is often used as a caricature of poorly written dialogue in movies and TV. Of course people want the truth, the criticism goes. At some point, at some level, every person realizes that they want the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing in Docpad</title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/static-text-generation/developing-in-docpad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 19:39:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/static-text-generation/developing-in-docpad/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve started developing in Docpad because I love lo-fi text-only documentation. This CMS uses folder structure and tags for site hierarchy and is very flexible. The MarkDown is transpiled into html and I can use a variety of templating languages for the layout components.
I&amp;rsquo;m going under the assumption that this will all provide maximal flexibility while I am actively creating content.
Lo-fi Conceptual Representations I write a lot of notes every single day in MarkDown and yaml.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/books/the_house_of_government/link/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/books/the_house_of_government/link/</guid>
      <description> affiliate link </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/democratization-or-liberalization/misinformed-democratization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/democratization-or-liberalization/misinformed-democratization/</guid>
      <description>Misinformed Democratization example citation [@krycho:revelation:2015, ¶6]
Examples of the misatribution of liberalization to democratization  Democracy can be defined as: &amp;gt; A system of government by the whole population or all the eligible members of a state, typically through elected representatives.
 After this definition, the meaning is distorted
 To put it more simply, democratic governments answer to their citizens. Through voting, people frame the institutions that govern them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://nofakingway.com/democratization-or-liberalization/whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nofakingway.com/democratization-or-liberalization/whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>Excluded Middle Whiteboard | Democratization | Liberalization | | Political Property | Private Property | | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;* | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;-* | | Majority Rule | Minority Rights | | Southern Democrats | Republicans | | Race Law | Abolishonism | | Production | | | Plantations/Slavery | Liberated Markets |
In the News  The Atlantic, &amp;ldquo;Is Democracy Dying&amp;rdquo;, special issue, 2018-10 Noam Chomsky, America&amp;rsquo;s foremost intellectual, Democracy threatened by liberalism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>